Mustafa Baban 1996

Residence: Iraq/Sulaymaniyah LinkedIn: <u>MustafaBaban</u>

Mail: mail@mstfa.me

Github: MustafaBaban

Portfolio: <u>mstfa.me</u> Behance: <u>mstfababan</u>

A skilled Full Stack Web Developer with a strong background in frontend development, experienced in working with various web technologies, and dedicated to creating elegant, efficient, and user-friendly applications. Proficient in English, Arabic, and Kurdish(Sorani) And basic proficiency in german.

SKILLS

- 1. Programming: JavaScript, PHP
- 2. Frameworks: Vue.js (Vue 2, Vue 3, Options API, Composition API), Laravel
- Design: CSS, SaSS, CSS Animations, Figma, Adobe XD, Mobile-first Responsive Design,
 CSS Libraries (Tailwind, Bootstrap), Modern Design Concepts
- 4. Git: Version and Branch Control
- 5. MVC Frameworks: Backend Development
- **6.** REST APIs: Development and Integration
- 7. UI/UX: Design and Implementation
- 8. Linux: Arch Linux and Terminal Use
- 9. Databases: SQL-based Databases
- 10. SEO: Routing Levels and Optimization
- 11. SSR: Implementation and Use Cases
- 12. SSG: CDN-based Builds
- 13. Accessibility: Inclusive Web Design
- 14. Communication: Teamwork and Problem-solving
- 15. Commitment: Lifelong Learning and Continuous Improvement

ACHIEVEMENTS

Hackathon: Hackasuly (2019), As Sulaymaniyah

First prize winner for the AI category.

EDUCATION

University of Human Development, Information Technology - Graduate

WORK EXPERIENCE

Rozhi spi, Sulaymaniyah

3 Months long in 2018

Position: Junior Developer(C# Fullstack)

 Developed the frontend and half of the backend for an accounting application, fulfilling all requirements.

Plus the edge, Sulaymaniyah

2019 - 2020

Position: Frontend Developer(Vue + Web design)

• Designed and developed frontends for various applications, including Hospital, Warehouse, and Restaurant Management Systems, as well as a restaurant food ordering app with PayPal integration.

Rudaw, Erbil 2021 - 2022

Position: Full Stack Web Developer(Vue + Web design and laravel backend)

- Designed and developed component-based Vue.js applications optimized for mobile use with a focus on smooth, efficient user experience.
- Implemented lazy loading, and data retrieval optimization using Redis caching.
- Optimized and refactored legacy code written by other developers.
- Employed Server-Side Rendering (SSR) and Static Site Generation (SSG) techniques to optimize website performance and SEO.

Moonline, Sulaymaniyah

2022 - 2023

Position: Frontend Web Developer(Vue + Web design)

- Surveyed SAP developers in order to create a custom form building solution using JSON and Strapi.
- Designed a schema for the form database and integrated it with the Strapi CMS to store and manage the form data.
- Conducted testing and debugging to ensure the solution was reliable and efficient.
- Provided documentation and training to the development team to enable them to create custom forms using the new solution.
- Collaborated with the development team to identify areas for improvement and made updates to the existing codebase to enhance performance and functionality.
- Debugged and resolved issues in the legacy code, while ensuring backward compatibility with the existing system.
- Developed new features and integrated them seamlessly with the existing codebase in a very short time.